{
    "subject": "resource/Irma_Elsa_Gonzalez",
    "predicate": "ontology/office",
    "object": "Chief Judge of theUnited States District Court for the Southern District of California",
    "human_readable": "Irma Elsa Gonzalez was the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789916276931763,
            "question": "In what district was Irma Elsa Gonzalez the Chief Judge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9538565278053284,
            "question": "Was Irma Elsa Gonzalez a judge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8568047881126404,
            "question": "Where was the United States District Court for the Southern District of California located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8200660943984985,
            "question": "What is the name of the court that Irma Elsa Gonzalez led?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7632372379302979,
            "question": "Which court did Irma Elsa Gonzalez preside over?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7526448965072632,
            "question": "What title did Irma Elsa Gonzalez hold in the court?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7113909125328064,
            "question": "What was Irma Elsa Gonzalez's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6043625473976135,
            "question": "Was Irma Elsa Gonzalez responsible for making legal decisions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5359361171722412,
            "question": "What was the highest position Irma Elsa Gonzalez held within the court?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4837547838687897,
            "question": "Did Irma Elsa Gonzalez work in a legal capacity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Irma Elsa Gonzalez was the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1421_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the highest position Irma Elsa Gonzalez held within the court?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1421_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Irma Elsa Gonzalez responsible for making legal decisions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1421_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Irma Elsa Gonzalez's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1421_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1421_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can answer as follows:\n\n* document 20.txt states that \"Judge Irma Elsa Gonzalez was appointed to the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of California in 1992...\" and document 33.txt states that \"She served as Chief Judge of the District Court from January, 2005 to January, 2012.\"\nTherefore, it can be inferred that Irma Elsa Gonzalez did serve as the Chief Judge of the United States District Court for the Southern District of California at some point in her career.\n\n* document 4.txt states that \"That year [2005], Gonzalez became chief judge in the Southern District of California...\" which further supports the inference above.\n\nThe answer is therefore:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Judge Irma Elsa Gonzalez served as Chief Judge of the District Court from January, 2005 to January, 2012, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}